You're the smartass
Duplass Brothers, aren't you?
How does the work break down?
What do you do?
All of our filming
happens right on the set.
-Very organic, in the moment,
like a therapy session.
Right.
We're improvising,
we're trying things,
we're getting upset and nervous
'cause it's not working.
We have a breakthrough.
"Holy shit!
This is so exciting!
It wasn't even in the script.
Let's go get it."
You know,
it's like the best version
-of what the scene could be
in this moment,
Right.
with the people we got
and where we're at.
We know what the scene
is supposed to be,
so let's just, like, see
what happens.
Hi.
Hi, I'm Naima,
I'm playing Natalie.
-How are you doing?
-Hello, good. How are you?
-Good. Welcome to set.
-Thank you.
Mark and Jay wanted
to talk to you before...
Yes, of course.
I wanna talk to them.
-Oh, thank you.
-Read this.
-And you don't get anything.
-Yeah.
I feel like all dentists
are like that.
-Hi, guys. Hi. Sorry.
-Hey.
-Hey. Jay. Nice to meet you.
-How are you?
Naima. "Nima,"
if you can call me that.
Naima, thank you
for being here.
We loved your tape,
it was awesome.
Oh, thanks. I'm so glad.
I'm such a big fan
of you guys. I'm...
Yeah, I'm just honored
to be here.
We're huge fan of yours.
How's life? What's going on?
You know, I've been up
all night, just kinda...
getting ready for this.
-Oh, boy.
-Yeah.
-We're kind of like--
- We're pretty easy
about everything.
We can totally get something.
-Hey.
-Oh, hello, geniuses.
Hi, sweetheart.
These guys are
Lindsay and Kamal.
-Kamal.
-Naima. You can call me Nima.
-Hey. Lindsay.
-Nima.
Uh, welcome to the set.
So we were talking
and doing the scene yesterday.
-It just felt a little...
It was different.
-Yeah.
-It would be great to block
It was fuckin'
incredible.
with the onion rings,
don't you think?
-I know it's just like a prop--
-Onion rings?
Yeah, I think there was
onion rings in the scene.
It was kind of
specifically noted.
-Oh.
-I don't even remember.
I think we just learned
maybe the onion rings
aren't that important.
-Right, yeah.
This is the first time in life
that onion rings
aren't important.
-Right.
Yeah, yeah.
There were a number of people
who wanted to talk to you.
Nobody wanted to talk to me.
Yes, they did.
And I think
there were, you know,
a lot of different things
going on tonight.
Tell me one...
What was the most...
Who was the cutest guy?
Okay. I know before we had
the whole thing,
where I was like,
you were pumped
that they went to the gay club.
It was a first time thing,
but, clearly,
things have changed,
and maybe less about
the onion rings?
Yeah.
I think the thing
to remember is that
Kamal is crushed
when he comes in,
and you need to respond
organically to that energy
and let go of the old version
of the scene.
I thought that...
all it took was me
to know I was gay,
and then I'd be gay.
But I don't know how
to talk to anyone. I don't--
Are you gay?
No, I think there were...
-Yeah.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, let's pause
for a second, guys.
-We're gonna pause real quick.
-We're gonna just come in
real quick.
Still rolling. Still rolling.
Well, just, while, like...
Um...
- Lindsay.
-Yeah, when Lindsay
is going to touch him,
if she makes it more clear...
-Right.
-...that she's hitting on him.
It's not really about her.
Your soulmate is coming undone
and you're here for him.
-Yes.
-Yeah, right?
And the more you can just be
an empathetic, open human being
that is receiving emotion,
that's all we need.
- He's in a great spot,
so once...
- Okay, okay.
Everybody good?
Let's get quiet on the set.
And, Naima,
you're just chilling.
How many have you put down?
I don't know,
but it is double figures.
Yeah!
Onion rings
without the onion
in the middle.
That's the worst part.
The onion is where
all the calories are, by the
way.
I swear it's the secret spot.
Hi. How's it going?
Hey, what's up?
Is it okay if I join you guys?
Yeah. Of course, yeah.
Ah.
Sorry it was a little
intense in there.
-No.
-Yeah.
I mean, it's just...
It's hard to get everyone
on the same page, you know?
Especially when it feels
like a little forced.
Mm-hmm.
I really feel like
with Kamal and, uh...
-Lindsay.
-Lindsay, right.
It's just that we have
very different acting styles,
I think.
We could, you know...
That's...
Talk about process and styles
and stuff like that.
I mean, at the end
of the day, you know,
we're happy with what
they're giving us,
-and it works for us.
-You are? Okay.
I mean,
all I can say is,
Jay and I were part
of a writers room one time,
and we got some notes
on our scripts,
and we went in and...
we told our showrunner
for an hour why he was wrong,
and why everything
he was telling us was idiotic.
And it didn't really
go well for us.
And we now realize
that we were probably being
a little defensive
and a little scared,
and that's okay.
I mean, we've kind of realized
that a lot of times
when you feel scared
or whatever,
you're actually right on
the precipice of, like,
an emotional breakthrough.
Yeah, I'm not...
I feel good.
I feel okay,
um, about it.
I had never been
on a set like that,
'cause, like, on commercials,
it's not like that.
But, like, the way
that Mark and Jay work,
it was like very...
It was so collaborative
right away.
It just made me feel like,
"Oh, this is what
it's supposed to be like."
Do you feel good about it?
Like...
Yeah. I feel great about it.
Do you think I look okay?
Yeah, you look fine.
Have you been talking
to this girl?
Yes, we've been texting.
Saw each other on the Internet,
and you know...
Right. Naturally.
Of course. I mean,
it's all in the hopes
of getting into some kind
of relationship, right?
But then, you wonder, like,
"Who did they actually
vote for?"
-You know, are they--
-Please don't bring up the...
What?
Like, the world is going
in the shitter.
You don't wanna talk about
what's actually happening
in the world?
Not on my first date
-with this girl that
I'm hopefully gonna like.
-Do I have a rule book?
Can you give me a check book
of what I'm supposed
to talk about?
How you guys doing?
Give the man a big
round of applause.
Are you ready to party?
Okay.
I have to bring
this young lady up.
She's always bringing
her ass in here,
wanting to sing with us.
She's from Spain.
I'm gonna let her do
this one damn song.
And her name is Sergio.
with an "O."
Hi.
This is my first song
I've written all in English.
And it's the first time
I'm gonna sing it to you.
So I'm, like,
a little bit nervous,
but I think it's gonna be
so cool.
I hope you like it.
Aw!
Bloom
My boy says make room
When the hand come
At the gloom
When the arm comes
Creeping up
I spread my arms so wide
Assume that
That forfeits doom
With the brightness
I resume
And my broken leaves
On my branches
Slips away
My blossoms bloom
Bloom, bloom, bloom, bloom
Okay! Wait, wait, wait.
I get it.
Andre, do you think
that's working?
Uh...
Oh, she's the only one.
-You are the truthful girl.
-Yes, I am.
Thank you so much.
It's very hard to have friends
that tell you the truth.
Okay. Let's make a deal.
Which is, like, a singer
you will go crazy about?
Stevie Nicks.
Okay. Let's pretend
I'm Stevie Nicks.
You like that?
Okay, I'm gonna
come down right now
and kiss you.
Oh, no!
We have a date.
Should we do it?
Should we do it, yeah?
Let's go.
That was so beautiful.
Whoo!
Come close, come close!
Come close, people!
Now, let's finish.
So I'm told
I've always been
With flashing flood
And whipping wind
I leave with everything...
It's ultimately a Ponzi scheme
that they created
for our environment.
-You know? Because--
What?
Well, meaning that, like,
past generations,
-the amount of coal
that they burn,
-Yeah.
it costs more in the effects
of climate change
than it costs to get it
out of the ground to use.
What?
It's just that all
our natural resources
were being used
in, you know,
you guys' heyday,
and now it's like
you took us out to dinner
and were like,
"Order everything you want.
Like, lobster tail, dessert,
it's on us."
And then you guys
snuck off to the bathroom
and never came back.
And, like, money
doesn't exist anymore.
-It was just a different time.
-But what's the solution?
After our natural
resources have gone,
it's just all gone.
There has to be a--
Jesus! You have a dark
view of the world.
-My God!
I'm just saying.
New York City, it's like
all these buildings
that are so tall and beautiful.
But people are gonna be,
like, fighting for trees.
Hey, do you wanna
dance with me?
That sounds
like a good idea.
I'm a little bit...
That sounds like
the perfect idea
to get your mind off of the...
Come on, let's go dance.
Go do it.
Shake a leg.
-Yeah.
Come on, now.
Go shake a leg.
Yeah.
-Okay.
Okay!
All right!
Can you guys watch
my jacket, though?
We'll watch your
natural resources over here.
Ha-ha! That's nice.
I'm Sergio.
Hi. Sergio, yeah.
I'm, I'm Naima.
You can call me Nima.
-Nima?
-Nima, yeah.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
I liked your show.
Maxine.
Wait, do you...
These were all your dogs?
Yeah, I foster them.
And then I find...
These are the final owners.
Like, the happy owners?
-Yeah.
I love you.
Do you like dogs?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Yeah, they're great.
It's okay if you don't.
What happened
to your friend?
She was
on a date, though.
-It was going well.
-Oh, cool.
Give me kiss.
Oh, I'm scared,
it went through my...
Five, four and go
Everybody's watching
Go, we're judging you
No pressure
Go
The explosively talented
-We do this all the time.
-Yeah.
We barely know you
Go
Anything.
I haven't been to the dentist
In over seven years
But I think that's okay
I feel truly superhuman
Every day
So good.
If I said right now
What I really meant
I guess I'd fall
Right down the stairs
And touch your head
I would really love
To touch your head right now
I would really...
We weren't officially
together or anything,
but it just felt good.
And then, she kind of,
in one swoop,
was, like, pretending
like were just friends
who had never shared
this intimate moment.
Then I pulled back,
because I guess
I don't wanna get hurt
or something.
Susanna has always, um...
Who's Susanna?
-My mom.
-Oh, your mom. Right, right.
Um, she has always
said to me,
try not to go
for the easy thing.
Like, everyone is doing this,
why you should do the same?
And that works in love.
You can't play it safe in love.
Yeah.
You have to just go
and tell them.
You know?
-You want food?
-No.
So I was dating this girl,
and after three years,
I find out
it was a waste of time.
So it was so fucked up.
Like, why I spent
three fucking years
of my life with this asshole?
Right.
So Susanna one day
said to me,
"You know those kind of couples
that they spend, like,
ten years together
and then they get married?
They divorce in one year."
-Right.
-So just get married
right away.
Yeah, do everything you want,
the second you want.
-Yeah.
I mean, you just get, like,
nervous thinking about it.
-before you do it.
-Exactly.
Just go and have fun
with the things
you have right there.
Yeah, like this.
This whole night.
We should do this
for, like, 24 hours straight.
-Like you and me?
-Yeah.
Eating chips, drinking juice.
-Having sex.
Let's do it.
-Now?
-I wanna know you, for real.
You got four hours
out of me so far.
I want 24 hours.
And I wanna come with you
every hour.
Hmm.
Isn't it amazing?
It's like dating ten years.
Yeah, we're gonna get
to go to the bathroom.
Sometimes I'm an hour
in the bathroom.
-I want to see you
taking a shit.
-Yeah.
I want to see you
getting angry.
We can do it.
We can fucking skip time.
Um, yeah.
I just have to work on Monday,
so we can't...
We can't...
Actually, you know what?
For your art,
to be busy with life,
it's the best thing
you can do.
I know. But I feel like
our whole bodies
are gonna be
outta whack by then.
It's the biggest job
I've ever had, so it's just...
-I can help you.
-I have to...
I practice alone.
It's embarrassing.
I can't.
I just can't.
It's a fun idea, though.
But...
Next time.
Yeah.
Instead of going
through the format
of regular dating,
and faking it,
and texting and stuff,
you know, it'd just be, like,
we would just be there
all the time.
I kinda think
it would be an amazing way
to get to know somebody.
Hmm.
I mean, I think I was realizing
I was, like, I haven't...
said yes to anything
in so long,
especially with somebody else,
because, like,
no one is even close
to her.
It's like she lives in a way
that she doesn't question
anything about herself.
And when I was around her,
I didn't either.
You should ask her
to go get some coffee
-tomorrow morning and just--
Oh, shit.
Oh, it's my manager.
-All right, let's go.
I'm starving.
-Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Right. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, wait.
It's transferring--
It's transferring
to a car coordinated--
Hello? Hey.
Are you there?
-Yeah, yeah.
Sorry. So, what were you saying?
Maybe I'm...
Maybe I'm soft-pedaling it
for you,
but they're gonna replace you.
What?
I know. I feel horrible.
I know you were
so excited about this,
and, you know,
sometimes on the first day,
when it's just not right
on an indie, you can't...
There's no time,
and so they have to move on.
They don't love you any less,
but it's not gonna work.
Okay, um...
I'll call you back.
Yeah. Okay.
It's okay. Yeah.
Hi.
It's me.
Sorry I didn't text
before I came over.
I just, um...
I was trying not to think
so much about it
and just come here.
Um, I needed to come
and say sorry
about what happened last night
and just, like, leaving
all awkwardly and...
You know, now I'm here.
We can hang out, you know?
Continue where we left off
and maybe even do the...
-Can I come in?
-No.
Okay.
Yeah, I feel...
This is the first place I drove,
you know what I mean?
I was just like, I wanted to...
I'm working on the backyard.
You have to go around.
Oh.
I know I fucked up.
But I'm here, I'm back.
I wanna stay up 24 hours
with you, 48 hours.
I haven't been able
to stop thinking about it.
We've got to do it.
What was your breakfast about
to make you change
your mind like this?
I had a high protein breakfast.
Normally I just have sugar.
I'm serious.
What changed?
The truth is that
I've never actually
gotten close enough
to somebody to love them.
That's the truth.
So it's just new for me,
that's all.
But that doesn't mean
I don't wanna try.
You know, I felt finally free
for a second last night.
Like I was actually
being myself.
And I just wanna do that.
So when you feel free,
you just run away?
I have, yeah.
-Will you do that again?
-No.
-Promise?
-Yes.
Promise?
I promise.
Okay.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
It's just eight o'clock.
I arrived at...
near 7:00 p.m.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
And sex every hour. Right?
-Can I touch you now?
-No.
-Hi.
-Hi, hi.
What's that?
It's a song that...
This is the song I want
to sing in the showcase.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Just-- You play piano?
Not really, no.
You were playing the piano.
I was just touching it.
You have to help me
with this song.
I know you can. I've heard you.
Okay.
I don't know. I can't...
My ears aren't too good, but...
Mm. Liar. Come on.
Struggling within
Quite a try and truth
Oh, how long it takes
Too high? Yeah?
That's good.
-Okay. So if I...
Come on, do it,
do it with both hands.
Maker of mistakes
I prayed and I felt it
Struggling with this
Quite a try and truth
Like, harmonize?
Oh, how long it takes
It's beautiful.
You have to sing
this song for me.
Okay.
Both of us together,
or aren't you singing?
No, you. Just you.
Okay.
Just back from the pill
Trying out a new brand
Oh...
Our costume is so absurd
Underneath the...
New sign
You have to suck this
right out of my body.
Is Sergio
your real name?
Yeah.
Why did your mom
name you Sergio?
She wanted a boy,
but I was a girl.
And then she thought,
"Okay, I'm gonna keep Sergio
in the middle name."
-Hmm.
-And when I was a kid,
and I wanted to have
Susanna's attention,
I took a shit.
-My shit was little shit,
because I was a kid.
-Sure.
And then I put this
little shit,
because my shits
were like this...
Yeah, and you cut it up
like a sausage or something?
Like a sausage.
So I put it on the floor
-and Susanna always thought
it was the dog.
-What?
Naima?
Look at me. Look.
You are so beautiful.
You're so, so...
so beautiful.
Say it.
Shout it.
Shout it to the fucking moon.
I can't.
Yeah, you can.
Say it to her.
-You have to say it with me.
-Yeah.
-I am so beautiful!
-She is so beautiful!
Stop being jealous!
Stop it!
The first time
I discovered masturbating
was on a sheepskin rug.
I would, like, rub up on it
while looking at myself
in the mirror.
I did the same with pillows.
-With pillows?
-Mm-hmm. With my cousin.
But then, her boyfriend
came and saw us.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Is your boyfriend still there?
He's still there.
So my friend
had her third kid.
And I was like, "How can you
still be having kids?"
It's like, you know the world
that you're birthing them into.
I just think
it's really selfish.
This is the kind of stuff
you were telling these ladies
at the bar. Why?
Why would somebody
have ten kids?
This thing is born
into the world,
and it's, like,
ruining their lives.
And they just pretend slowly
-Stop.
-that it doesn't...
Okay.
-Don't you think every parent
hates their kid?
-No.
People eventually
are going to be starving.
We have an end, you know.
There's an end.
So, what we can do
till now?
Get depressed about it?
I think I feel more
connected to people
when I feel like we're both
on the same page.
I think you depress people
when you're talking about that.
So I'm not supposed
to depress people?
I'm supposed to, like...
-make 'em happy?
-What do you think?
Every day I wake up
and I'm reading the news,
and it's just like one more
depressing thing after another.
What are you doing?
Are you doing something?
You can help Maxine.
I feel like I just want
to turn into a soldier,
where someone knocks
at my door one day and is like,
"It's over. Here's your weapon.
Let's go."
And I'd go.
But until then, I'm...
I'm knocking at your door.
God, no!
Stop!
Stop. Let's be friends.
The war is not happening yet.
The people we--
Oh, my God!
That's so disgusting!
It's wet. It's hot.
It's hot. It's hot.
Okay, baby. I stop. I stop.
Promise. Promise.
Seriously, stop.
Tell me, what is more scary?
The end of the world
or this shit?
Right now this shit,
right now.
Are there people back there?
Let's go and do it
in front of them.
What?
-No.
-Yes.
We hide.
Okay.
Just act normal.
It's so good to see you.
Yeah,
it's been too long.
I thought you'd changed
your number or something.
No, I've just been so wrapped up
in work these days.
I remember
the last time I saw you
was at Jeremy's house,
when we did sake bombs
and then I threw up
on Cindy's jacket.
You always seem to be
very sociable.
I was just slutty is the truth.
But it's worked out for me now.
"Slutty"?
Sergio, I have to get one take.
Just because the boy
is saying to you
you're sociable,
you say you are slutty?
I mean, I don't...
It's not a good movie.
It's not a good movie
then why you wanna do it?
'Cause I need a job.
You should really do stuff
you wanna do.
If not, you are just
giving these people
just your talent for nothing.
You are giving a presentation
of who you are.
I think you should just
e-mail these guys
and tell them, "Look--"
I can't e-mail.
The last time I told--
-"You are a fucking
misogynist."
-No.
And just go and start
writing your own movie,
telling something
you have inside.
Recently when I told somebody
what I about thought 'em,
I got fired.
You got fired because
you said them what you thought?
Yeah. And I didn't think
it was going well,
so at lunch, I like,
talked to them about it,
and it just did not go well.
Okay, then fuck this tape.
Come, e-mail these guys.
-No, I have to do this tape.
-Really, I'm telling you.
You should e-mail
those guys who fired you
and tell them
why they are wrong.
I mean, they won't
take you seriously
if you don't say, "No."
They fired you.
They will never ever
hire you again.
So, what can you lose?
Yeah.
-Tell them!
-Okay.
So, okay. As an artist...
And I'm talking
to an artist too.
-As an artist speaking...
-To an artist.
...to other artists,
because there's two of them.
Other artists.
You know that the most
important is to be honest
with the work
The most important...
I want to be...
I want to work on movies
that respect...
-"I will make movies."
-...honesty.
I will make movies.
"And they will respect artists."
And they will respect artists.
"And then I will come
to your fucking door,
-and knock-knock."
-And then I will... Okay.
"Come to your fucking door
and knock-knock"?
Where does that one end?
"I'm gonna come to your door
and knock, knock," and what?
"And knock-knock to your door
and tell you..."
Fuck you?
-Yeah! Good!
-I mean...
"I will make movies.
Ones that respect artists.
And then I will come
to your door..."
All caps. "Knock-knock,
and say, 'Fuck you.'"
Okay.
-Should I send it?
-Yeah.
Wait, wait. No, no, no. Wait.
Okay. What are you gonna do?
-Record a sound.
Are you recording?
-What?
Oh. Okay. Yeah, yeah.
Send it, send it.
It's 2:00 a.m.
So what?
Means we have 17 hours to go.
I once met
an older gentleman.
He was, like,
a respected writer.
I was a fan of his,
and we started e-mailing
and it was kind of
just like pen pals.
And they were kind of funny.
They were, like, dirty e-mails.
And then I was
in New York once.
Told him I was there
and he wrote back
right away, like,
"Come over to my house."
He opened the door
and he had this real fake,
slick air about him.
And he was kind of leaning
on the door, like...
"Come on in."
But in that moment I realized...
I had complete control
over him, you know?
And I remember his kids
were sleeping in the other room,
so we had to go
into the guest room.
But you were there
to fuck him?
I didn't decide,
but once I walked in, I was...
I was like, that's what's
gonna happen.
-Yeah.
-Like I was there
to deliver something.
In exchange of what?
It was like I wanted
his respect or something.
But definitely
didn't get it by...
having sex with him.
Yeah. Was it good?
No, it was terrible.
-Really?
-Yeah, it was really bad.
Fuck, that sucks.
He started to go
down on me and...
came up and he was like
disturbed all of a sudden.
He...
pretty much said that...
there is too much, like...
uh, smegma.
-It's gross. It's like...
-Soft?
Yeah, it's a little like
cottage cheesy.
Like mantequilla de pato.
Manteqa de pato?
Mantequilla de pato.
It's like duck butter.
Duck butter.
-Duck. Quack, quack.
-Right, right.
-I like that better.
-So, what happened?
He didn't like that?
He didn't like my duck butter.
And so he kind of like
awkwardly stood up
and left the room.
You should send him
a box with a pint of
mantequilla de pato.
-Just like a gift wrap?
-Yeah.
A present for his kid.
They can eat it.
I'll say,
"Happy Thanksgiving." Yeah.
Duck butter for your kids.
So I wanted to do a record
and I had no money.
So I made a deal with this guy,
a very successful businessman.
"You pay for my record
for three months,
and then I can be
your girlfriend."
That was our deal.
And what'd you have to do
with him?
I lived with him,
I slept with him.
For three months.
And at the end,
he stopped paying
for my record.
-Oh, man.
-Yeah, I know.
So I tape him
having sex with me,
and then I said to him,
"Okay, if you don't pay
for my record,
I'm going to show this
to everyone."
So he paid.
Yeah.
And then you just
stopped it and left?
Yeah.
All right.
What's that?
It's my face.
I love it.
I picture myself having sex
with a lot of people.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Like, with my friends.
-Mm.
-I think it's so hot.
Yeah.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
I think I've...
I think I've come too much.
We'll do it again.
Maybe I just need
a little break.
No problem. Don't worry.
You were sleeping like this.
-Yeah.
-Right? Yeah.
You are so sleepy.
-Yeah...
-Don't worry.
No, no, no.
Stop it! Seriously.
Stop, stop. Stop.
Fuck off.
You okay?
Yeah. I, um...
I don't really feel
so good. Like...
I just feel a little, um...
I don't know. I don't know.
It's just...
Because of the sleep?
I think it was the combination
of the sleep and just...
staying awake.
I feel like I don't have
a lot, um...
a lot of brain power left to...
to even, like,
communicate anything.
It's because of me something?
It's because you're feeling
weird about me?
No, no, no.
But if you are, you can say it.
No, that's totally
not the reason, no.
What's going on, then?
You know...
I think it was just like,
you know, today it was like...
Like, I got fired earlier today,
and when I woke up...
You got fired today?
Yeah, this morning.
This morning you got fired.
'Cause you said recently.
Yeah.
So...
you got fired
and then you came here?
There was time in between,
but, yeah.
You came here
because you got fired.
No, that's not the reason
why I came here.
Yeah.
It is.
No.
No, it's not...
It's not like...
I mean...
I found out this morning...
I think you should go.
-Now.
-Yeah.
This will cleanse us.
Why do we have
to stay up all night?
-We have to.
-Yes.
Are you close with your mom?
Yeah. We talked every day.
Yeah?
-She's coming.
-What?
She's coming for the showcase.
So I have to have breakfast
with her tomorrow.
-Oh, no.
-Today.
Right.
We were supposed to go
to the Seven tomorrow.
What do we do?
Do we break the...
Oh.
I don't know.
You will be there
in the showcase?
Promise? Okay?
Of course.
Susanna, when I was four,
we were in the street,
and I said to her
that I wanted normal mom.
And she said to me,
"Okay, just go and find her."
And she left me
in the middle of the street.
When you were four?
I spent the whole afternoon
trying to find the way
back home.
And then a neighbor found me.
And my mom said to me,
"Did you find her?"
And I was like...
And she said, "Good,
because I don't want
a normal daughter."
She said, "I don't want
a normal daughter"?
Yeah.
Whew.
How about your mom?
She's pretty like...
kind of strong, loud lady
from the Middle East.
She came over,
like, in the '70s.
But I got along better
with my dad.
Why?
She didn't really like the way
that I was like...
kind of a tomboy in school
and... I don't know.
Are you angry with her?
I think I have a lot of anger
with her, but I, like...
Have you talked
about that with her?
No.
Yeah, but that's inside.
This anger is there.
For a time.
Have you done meditation?
No, I haven't.
It kind of freaks
me out, you know.
-You do it?
-Yeah.
When I'm getting
anxious, like...
Like an anxiety attack,
I start thinking like a river
is crossing over me,
and I start describing
this river, and then...
I try to change the river
into a new river.
How is your river?
-My river is so brown.
-Oh, it's so chunky.
-It's brown...
-Yeah, I got brown, chop--
All the time, during that,
coming out of my...
Yeah, it's loud, it's choppy.
Okay, sit up.
Okay, you have your mom
in front of you.
-Okay, yeah.
-Just tell her
all the shit you wanna
make sure she knows.
Susanna, you're fucking crazy
leaving me at four years old
in the fucking street.
You're a fucking crazy mom.
For example.
Okay.
I think you're really angry
about how your mother
was to you
and you take it out on me.
And you're just a mean,
stupid bully
who teases
your innocent daughter.
Just go and tell her things.
I think you're jealous of me.
And that's why you're just
talking to me every fuck--
-You have to keep going.
-Right, right, right. Sorry.
I think you don't
take care of yourself.
-Yeah.
-You're super unhealthy
and you take it out on me,
and you blame me for not
being in better shape.
-You're a fucking narcissist.
-You smell disgusting
all the time,
and you blame me
for smelling bad.
Maybe you should be proud
about me for one fucking day.
You never accomplish shit.
And you never have
loved my dad ever,
and you pretended like
you have always,
and it's fake
and he doesn't like you.
You've never liked him!
Ever!
I'm never gonna have fucking
kids until you're dead!
-What time is it?
-It's like 6:00 something.
Susanna is coming.
Like, for breakfast?
This house is a mess.
Why don't we just...
Why don't we go to my house?
I have a bunch of food
at my house.
My house is like, clean,
like a hotel,
because I barely live in it.
What do you think?
Is that a good idea?
I can cook.
I go by my bike.
I'm following you.
All right.
Oh, my God!
Whoa!
Okay, let go.
I'm gonna jump inside of you.
Sergio, no, no, no.
It's too close.
No, stay at least that far.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Don't go inside.
Come on, open the door.
-That's enough.
-Open the door.
Just let me get the--
Oh, my God.
You live alone?
Yep.
It's so... big.
My dad got it for me.
He bought a lot
of real estate years ago,
and gave me and my sister
a house.
Are you judging me for having
such a nice house?
No, I want it for me.
Whoa, what's that?
It's a painting my dad did.
It's depressing, right?
I don't know.
I kinda like it.
I don't understand
how can you live with this.
I know, but I feel bad.
Like, my dad would feel sad
if it was gone.
You have to just take
this ugly stuff
out of your life.
This is what is wrong
with your life.
-Just take it off.
-Yeah.
Be careful. Sergio.
Whoa! Sergio.
-Whoa! Sergio. Sergio.
I guess I'm never having
my dad over again.
I don't care if it's
your dad's picture.
It's just depressing,
so just fuck it.
Burn it.
I feel, like, so powerful
in this place.
It's so white.
-We have, like, an hour.
-Yeah.
-Time to play.
-Okay.
What?
Okay. It's okay.
What's wrong?
-Breathe.
-It's nothing.
I'm just tired.
-Sure?
-Yeah.
It's me. You can tell me.
Are we okay?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
We're okay, yeah.
I just... Yeah. I don't know.
I'm just tired.
Susanna is coming, you know.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Don't worry.
-It's okay.
-Okay.
-Okay, let's calm down.
-Yeah.
I'll take a shower.
You go cook something,
and then Susanna arrives.
Yeah.
Can you, can you be here
with me for that?
Sorry, I'll be okay.
-Okay. Sure?
-Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
Yeah.
Naima.
Do you have
another brush? Look.
The fucking brush
is broke.
Look at that.
It's fucking broken.
Here. Stop, stop, stop.
Hold it so it doesn't...
Sorry, I thought I had
more breakfasty food.
I'm making, like,
gnocchi and salad.
You think Susanne
is gonna eat this?
It's like potato.
-And I have a pesto sauce.
-Yeah, I know what is gnocchi.
I know.
Is she gonna be okay
with just having some
random grub here?
She's coming over
to a stranger's house.
She doesn't know me
or anything.
No, no. She's so cool.
She's so good with everything.
She just deals with everything.
Fuck!
What's that?
-Hmm?
-Music.
It's this song called...
"Ah! Sweet Mystery Of Life."
It's a like really old
1920s song,
but covered by...
-Cover?
-Yeah.
But the first version sounds
a little different than this.
You don't like it?
I don't do covers.
You don't do covers?
No.
People who does covers
they're just doing
bullshit copying someone else.
-What about Elvis?
-What?
Almost every song
he did was a cover.
The fact that his...
The way he sang those songs
had nothing to do
with how beautiful they were.
If anyone else sang it,
they wouldn't be good songs.
And, yeah,
he's an interpreter,
not an artist.
Beatles were creating
something new.
Not fucking Elvis.
-Do you have wine?
-Yes.
Do you have water?
Yes.
We'll have to fill it up.
Uh...
What? What's missing?
That's it, right? That's it.
I mean, what else--
Yeah, it looks great.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
You know, we haven't had sex
in, like, two and a half hours.
Hola.
-Hi.
-She's Naima.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
You will love it.
Have you heard any
of her latest songs?
Yeah, I have.
Yeah, I love 'em.
And what do you think?
Because she did such
beautiful things
when she started.
She... She was totally
uncompromising.
So strong.
And then...
But now
I'm writing a lot here.
-Really?
-Yeah, and I'm painting
a lot too.
And you think that you
found your voice here?
You have something
to say here?
Speak in English.
In English. Naima is right here.
-Susanna!
Come on. I didn't want
to upset you.
Ah! Well...
One thing I was thinking about,
you know, I belong
to a generation,
we grew up without AIDS
and all these things.
We could allow ourselves
a lot of things that these days
young people cannot do.
And you know
I'm a Mediterranean,
and there is this tradition
in the Mediterranean countries
that in the spring
everybody used to gather
in the fields and just fuck.
They thought that
that was what made
the earth grow.
And I like to keep
that tradition alive, you know.
-Mm.
-Sex is so enjoyable.
And I think the reason why
is that it's so impersonal.
It's not like love, you know.
Like, you don't have
to be picking up
and, "I need you."
No. It's more free.
Sergio and I love
arguing about that.
I hope you're enjoying her.
Okay. Are you better now?
So are you also
an artist, Naima?
Uh, yeah, I'm an actress...
mainly, yeah.
She also plays the piano.
She does?
Yeah.
Sergio?
I'm sorry, I forget the iPad.
Thank you.
Thank you, Naima.
It's like something happened.
I don't know what is it,
but it's like...
my mind pfft.
So, so beautiful.
It's almost hard to touch you.
It's like I'm like here
and it's like...
hard to touch you.
I've already started writing
a song about us.
-Really?
-Yeah.
What's it about?
It's about you and me
falling in love
for the first time.
But, like, we have invented
falling in love.
You know? We invented it
and the rest just copied us.
Like doing covers
of our falling in love.
I'm sorry about the...
about the covers before.
-It's okay.
-I'm sorry.
Hug me.
I gotta go pee.
No, no, pee here.
-Pee here.
-Pee here?
I'll come be with you.
I'll be right back.
Oh, my God. Okay.
Naima. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Okay. Sure?
-Okay.
-Yeah.
You know what? For Christmas,
Kathy and Faye, they're doing
a road trip for Europe.
Road trip in Europe? Wow.
We should go with them.
Maybe.
Maybe?
Yeah, we still got, you know...
It's in the future.
We'll figure it out later.
-Okay.
-Yeah. Okay.
You've never, like...
been with Kathy, or...
or Faye before, have you?
-Been with them? Yeah?
-Like?
-Physically.
Like, have you had sex
with them before?
-No.
-No?
No.
Why?
I don't know.
I was just thinking, like...
maybe they...
could come for like the...
the end, you know?
Like the last two hours,
or something like...
I've never done an orgy.
That would be fun.
Do you wanna do an orgy now?
I don't know.
I think it could be intr--
I think it'd just be like
a nice book end.
It could be really fun.
I'll be right out.
I don't wanna do an orgy.
Okay.
Okay. Let me pee.
Okay. I mean,
let's talk about it.
Yeah, let me just pee.
-Yeah?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Sure?
Yes.
-Okay.
-Yeah, yeah.
Sergio?
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine, Sergio.
But I'd rather not be
in the bathroom.
Can you let go
of the handle, please?
Why do you want
to do an orgy?
It was just an idea!
I mean, we were trying...
I don't know.
I don't think that seems
like the weirdest thing.
You know,
it's just something new
that we could do together.
I thought you would be into it.
I thought it would
bring us closer.
But that's it.
I just want us
to be closer, Sergio.
That's all.
Sergio?
Sergio!
It's okay.
[Kathy] How are you?
You seem good.
Yeah.
It's really... You know,
we have little naps,
but it's been pretty.
-Yeah, well...
-Yeah.
Have you guys done something
like this before, or...
-It's been a while.
-Yeah.
I've, like, failed
at it a few times.
Seems like a good time.
I know it's midday, but...
I prefer that.
-Yeah.
It's so cliche
of, like, the night.
I like to see everything.
Yeah.
So... are we on a timer?
We can start.
We could just do...
-the old hello.
-Mmm.
-I love you.
Mmm. Hi.
Is it weird?
Um...
Hello.
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, yeah.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. I...
Sorry about that.
-No problem.
-It's okay.
Come.
Yeah, I just...
got distracted.
-Which happens.
-Yeah.
I mean, I think it's...
-No, it wasn't.
It had nothing to do
with you guys. I just...
I'm really glad
you guys are here.
Yeah.
-Because I think that...
Because you guys
are close to Sergio,
just, like, this has been
a lot for us.
And I think that
if you guys stayed,
we could talk, like...
We don't...
You know, what are we
really gonna offer?
Right? I mean,
I just feel like...
-I think just support.
-It would make sense
for us to maybe...
I think support, though,
and I think Sergio
maybe wants you here.
I think we should all
talk about this together.
-What do you think?
-Yeah. Do you want us to stay?
-Um... no, no.
-Yeah.
I feel like maybe
you guys should,
um, just talk.
-It's totally fine.
-Yeah.
-We will talk later.
-I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
-It's fine.
-Thank you.
-I'm so sorry.
-No.
-Don't worry about it.
-Okay.
Will you call me later?
Yeah. Sure.
Okay.
I have to go to the bathroom.
So do I.
-Say hi to my shit
right now.
-What?
Oh, my God!
Is that your own shit?
It's my own shit
in your fucking face.
-How's that? How's that?
-Stop it! You're fucking crazy!
Stop it!
-Be honest!
-No!
What are you--
Oh, my God!
No! Stop it.
What the fuck? Don't...
-Okay, be honest.
-What do you want me to say?
To say what you're thinking.
I don't want to do this.
I don't want to do any of this.
You scare me, Sergio.
Thank you.
Thank you for being honest
for one fucking minute
in 24 hours.
Thank you!
You're so fucked up.
I have to take a shit
and put it in
your fucking face
for you to say the things
as they are.
I've been 24 hours
trying you to be honest.
Being with you.
Being real next to you.
Why are you trying so hard?
I don't want you to.
Because I fucking love you.
How do you know?
-Yes--
-No, you don't.
Because it's fucking here!
Because it hurts!
Because it hurts so much.
That's why I know.
It's fucking real, okay.
-Stop.
-Okay? Stop, just--
Stop!
You have to stop.
I don't wanna do it.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Any of it.
The coastline sight
just blamed the majority
of the increase
on rising sea levels
caused by global warming.,
and they say the flooding
will only get worse.
But predicting where
those beach or floods will hit
has only just begun.
Our own Chris Donnelly reports.
Almost 50 times a year,
Casco Bay floods the port city
of Portland, Maine where--
Hi.
I'm gonna now sing this song
uh... yeah.
I didn't write it,
but neither did Elvis.
Suppose the springtime
Should not arrive
Suppose the tall
Green trees
Should not survive
Suppose I had no wish
To be alive
Suppose you didn't
Love me
Hey.
You got a home, bud?
Your name is not Maxine, is it?
Love you.
Good night, good night.
Ah! Sweet mystery of life
At last, I've found you
At last I know
The secret of it all
For the longing, seeking
Striving, waiting, yearning
The burning hopes
The joy and idle tears
That fall
For it's love and love alone
The world is seeking
And it's love and love alone
That can repay
It's the answer
It's the end
And all of living
For it is love alone
That rules the day
Sweet mystery of life
Sweet mystery